https://collegeofsanmateo.edu/generalinformation/privacypolicy.asp

Privacy Policy
Please read the following carefully. This page provides general information about the privacy policy of this website.
The contents of this website are owned and operated by College of San Mateo (CSM), located at 1700 W. Hillsdale Boulevard, San Mateo, CA, 94402. You can contact us by email at csmwebmaster@smccd.edu. CSM is very concerned about the protection of online privacy for all our website visitors and especially children. CSM's policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. This statement tells you if and how we collect personally-identifying information from you and how we use it. Using the internet should be a fun and safe experience and we want to help you make it so.
What information is collected?
We consider the following to be personally-identifying information: your first and last name, email address, home address, phone number, social security number and if linked with your other personally-identifying information, your date of birth and other personal interests and hobbies.This website does not collect personally-identifying information about a user except for information that is voluntarily provided to us so that we can serve the user's needs and our legitimate business and/or educational purposes. A user's personally-identifying information may be used by CSM to help us improve the website. CSM does not collect personal information for marketing or advertising purposes. It will be treated confidentially within our institution. Our policy is not to share this information with third parties.If you submit a form or send email to CSM, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Occasionally, CSM may ask visitors to participate voluntarily in surveys that we use for research purposes. If personal information is included in these surveys, a link to this Privacy Statement will be included.
What are cookies?
Cookies are a small file located on the user's computer that provides the web server with information about you to help customize the site for you. Cookies can store and sometimes track information about you. A small amount of data is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. When you return to a website, the cookie informs the web server who you are and what your preferences are and can then customize your browsing experience for that specific website.The CSM web server does collect IP addresses for system administration purposes, to track system usage, or for security purposes. These IP addresses are kept in a log file and are a normal part of the web server. This information will not be distributed or shared with any third party unless directed by court order.
Will CSM share my personal information?
As a general rule, no. CSM will not disclose any personal information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. CSM does not sell or rent your information to anyone. CSM also does not share, rent or sell your personal financial or health-related information.
CSM Home
|
About CSM
|
Accessibility
|
Apply & Enroll
|
1700 W. Hillsdale Boulevard, San Mateo, CA 94402    (650) 574-6161
